ilounge.com 2018-06-24

# iLounge Privacy Policy

The policies below are applicable to iLounge. Any questions or comments you may have regarding this privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.ilounge.com/index.php/ilounge/contact/).

iLounge respects each individual user's right to privacy. iLounge does not collect personal identifying information unless such information is specifically and knowingly provided from users during contests, surveys, sweepstakes, giveaways, site registration, or use of public areas, such as a forum. iLounge may use aggregate forms of this information -- not individual data -- for marketing and promotional purposes. iLounge does not supply identifying information to other companies, or uses such information for its own purposes including but not limited to email newsletters, unless the user "opts-in" for such purposes by specifically allowing usage. (Identifying information must necessarily be used when notifying a user of requested information, such as notification of a winning entry in a contest or sweepstakes.) iLounge is not responsible for any actions or policies of such companies.

iLounge uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us secure. However, iLounge is not responsible for any breach of security. If a iLounge user knowingly provides personal information, such as a name or email address, in a forum or other public service, that user should be aware that the information provided can be collected and used by third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of iLounge.

Non-personal information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of iLounge's Internet servers or through the use of "cookies." Cookies are small text files a web site places on your computer's hard drive to recognize repeat users and facilitate the user's use of the site. Also, cookies allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data for content improvement, targeted advertising, and marketing and promotional purposes. Users should be aware that iLounge cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or other third parties. Most browsers allow a user to deny cookies; however, users should note that cookies may be required to provide certain web site features.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

ATTENTION KIDS: No information should be submitted to iLounge by children under 18 years of age without their parent's or guardian's consent. iLounge does not monitor the age of its user audience.

iLounge reserves the right to change this policy at any time by posting notice of the existence of a new privacy statement. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

Last updated 07|08|14

### Recent News

  * [Report: Apple actively seeking to phase out Lightning connector on future iPhones](http://www.ilounge.com/index.php/news/comments/report-apple-actively-seeking-to-phase-out-lightning-connector-on-future-ip "Report: Apple actively seeking to phase out Lightning connector on future iPhones")
  * [AirPower to run stripped down version of iOS, now expected to arrive in September](http://www.ilounge.com/index.php/news/comments/airpower-to-run-stripped-down-version-of-ios-now-expected-to-arrive-in-sept "AirPower to run stripped down version of iOS, now expected to arrive in September")
  * [Apple developing kids’ programming in partnership with Sesame Workshop](http://www.ilounge.com/index.php/news/comments/apple-developing-kids-programming-in-partnership-with-sesame-workshop "Apple developing kids’ programming in partnership with Sesame Workshop")

  * [Apple Pay goes live in Norway, Poland; may be coming soon to Czech Republic](http://www.ilounge.com/index.php/news/comments/apple-pay-goes-live-in-norway-poland-may-be-coming-soon-to-czech-republic "Apple Pay goes live in Norway, Poland; may be coming soon to Czech Republic")
  * [Kristen Wiig departs upcoming Apple comedy amidst scheduling conflicts](http://www.ilounge.com/index.php/news/comments/kristen-wiig-departs-upcoming-apple-comedy-amidst-scheduling-conflicts "Kristen Wiig departs upcoming Apple comedy amidst scheduling conflicts")
  * [U.S. Supreme Court to hear Apple appeal of App Store antirust case](http://www.ilounge.com/index.php/news/comments/u.s.-supreme-court-to-hear-apple-appeal-of-app-store-antirust-case "U.S. Supreme Court to hear Apple appeal of App Store antirust case")

### Recent Reviews

### Recent Articles

  * [Sponsored: 8 iPhone and Apple Watch chargers that reduce clutter](http://www.ilounge.com/index.php/articles/comments/sponsored-8-iphone-and-apple-watch-chargers-that-reduce-clutter "Sponsored: 8 iPhone and Apple Watch chargers that reduce clutter")

  * [Inside the betas: iOS 11 Control Center gets customizable, adds Screen Recording](http://www.ilounge.com/index.php/articles/comments/inside-the-betas-ios-11-control-center-gets-customizable-adds-screen-record "Inside the betas: iOS 11 Control Center gets customizable, adds Screen Recording")
  * [Inside the betas: iOS 11 HomeKit adds timers, multi-person occupancy support](http://www.ilounge.com/index.php/articles/comments/inside-the-betas-ios-11-homekit-adds-timers-multi-person-occupancy-support "Inside the betas: iOS 11 HomeKit adds timers, multi-person occupancy support")
  * [Inside the betas: tvOS 11 adds auto Dark Mode, iCloud Home Screen Sync](http://www.ilounge.com/index.php/articles/comments/inside-the-betas-tvos-11-adds-auto-dark-mode-icloud-home-screen-sync "Inside the betas: tvOS 11 adds auto Dark Mode, iCloud Home Screen Sync")
